My name is Joe Holdcroft, and I lead one of our software engineering teams.
I've been here almost two years.
I worked with Guy and several of the early folks at Snyk before.
It's quite an exciting prospect to get to work with some of these folks again.
since then things have changed a lot.
We’re a fair bit bigger.
We've gone through a number of sort of different prototypes that we've built,
a number of different products that we've put together.
And we're just now sort of starting to get to the point where it feels like
there's a bit of traction.
We're sort of heading towards finding product market fit.
You know, as you'd sort of expect in a startup environment,
there's lots of ability to influence change and impact the product.
And I feel like that's especially the case here.
It's a really nascent space, we're building a tool for software
engineers, we are software engineers, All ideas are good ideas.
There's plenty of space to, like,
go and prototype something if you want to have a play.
Like, you don't just have to go and show this to
somebody, you can actually, like, build it.
And especially with the current AI tooling,
you can really put something together in a short period of time
that you can then actually go and productionize.
So, a lot of the product development is actually like grassroots
development that comes from the software engineering team.
There was something that we announced a couple of weeks ago,
And that just came out of one of our developers
putting in a bit of time and putting something together
and just kind of people seeing that and getting their hands on it
made us realise how valuable it was.
So, invested a bit more time on it.
And, you know, in the space of under a week
that went from a little hobby project that he’d thrown together, to something
that we released and did a marketing campaign about.
One of the most important and notable parts
of the culture, I think is, the level of proficiency.
A lot of people here, like, have a bunch of experience in software development,
in like dev tooling companies, and/or like in the AI space.
So, I'm constantly learning things from the people around me.
And I think especially in this time where the nature of the role is changing
so rapidly, it sort of brings me a lot of comfort
to feel like I'm working with, like, some of the best, best in class folks.
Yeah.
Like I say, one of the things that drew me to the company
and one of the things that keeps me here.